Guide to the Fedor Stepun Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Schlippe, Yura
Schlitter, D.
Schlocker, Georges
Schlosstheater Celle
Schluter, Andreas
Schmauss, A. (Deutsche Gesellschaft fur Osteuropa Kunste)
Schmeetz, Erich
Schmeetz, Hans-Gerd
Schmid, Karl
Schmid Noeur, Elisabeth
Schmidt, Emil
Schmidt, Gerhard
Schmidt-Heinze, H.
Schmidt-Pauli, Kurt Edgar von
Schmidtlein, Maria
Schmitt, Joh.
Schmitt-Sulzthal, Rudolf
Schmitz-Egelhaaf, Alfred
Schmücker, Ingeborg
Schmuecker, Marie-Therese
Schnabel, Rudolph
Schneider-Fassbaender, Martha
Schockenhoff, Heinz
Schoenrich, Christa
Schoepf-Witting, Sibylle
Scholl, Elisabeth
Scholl, Günther
Scholl, Robert
Scholz, Karl
Schönberg, Michael von
Schoneck, Hans
Schondorff, Joachim Schöner wohnen Schopen, Edmund
Schopke, Artur (Artur Shepke)
Schorer, Maria
Schottlaender, Felix
Schrader, Hansgeorg
Schraeder, Irmgard
Schramm, Karin
Schreiber, Hans
Schreieg, Anton
Schreiter, Theo
Schremmer, Ernst
Schröder, H.
Schröder, Theodor-Werner
Schröpfer, Johann
Schröter, Max
Schubart Buchhandlung
Schubert, Adelheid (A. Dorn)
Schubert, Ernst
Schubert, Walter
Schubert, Wilhelm
Schubring, S.
Schuester, Michael
Schüle, Emil
Schuler-Kleiner, F.
Schult, Herta
Schulte-Bisping, Hildegard
Schultz, Albert
Schultz, Hans Jürgen
Schulze-Battmann, Elfriede (Landesamt für Museen)
Schulze-Battmann, Eva
Schulze-Buxloh, F.
Schulze-Kaiser, ??
Schulzle, Josef
Schumacher, Ernst
Schumann, Hans
Schunk, H.
Schüpfer, Johann
Schupp, Gisela
Schurig, Walter
Schütt, F.
Schütte, Ehrenfried
Schütz, Johannes
Schütze, Johannes
Schutze, Fritz Schwäbische Donau Zeitung Schwalbe, M.
Schwann. Pädagogischer Verlag und Druckerei
Schwarz, ?
Schwarz, Alfred
Schwarz, Ernst
Schwarz, Fritz
Schweighoffer, F.
Schweizerischer Buchhandler- und Verlagerverein
Schwerte, H.
Sedlmayer, Hans
Seeger, Ingeborg and Arno
Seeliger, Lieselotte
Segal, R.
Seger, I.
Sehrwald, Margarita von
Seidelmeier, Heinz
Seidlein, Karen von
Seifart, Maria
Seifert, Rudolf
Seiffert, August
Seikendorff, Baronin von
Selenisch, Jutta
Semenov, Mikhail Nikolaevich Der Senator für Volksbildung Sender Freies Berlin
Sennewald, Lothar
Senning, A.
Settenmeyer, ?
Seyboth, Hermann
S"ezd Rossiiskikh Zarubezhnykh Deiatelei
Shik, Aleksandr
Shmelev, Vsevolod
Shteininger, Aleksandr
Shtraus, Elena (with letter from N. M. Borovskaia)
Siebeck, Hans Georg
Sigsfeld, Irmgard von
Siemens, Christian
Siewerth, Gustav
Sikk, August
Sill, Hans
Siller, Ruth
Simaiti, A.
Simon, W.
Sinz, Max
Sivers, E. von
Sivers, Margaret[e] von
Skalon, N.
Skogholm, Carl Werner
Skonietzki, Rudolf
Slanina, Ernst W.
Slavisches Institut (München)
Sleptsova, A.
Sleptzov, Platon Alekseevich Oiunskii
Societa Italiana di Sociologia
Societas Hobbesiana
Söhngen, Josef
Soiuz Bor'by za Osvobozhdenie Naradov Rossii
Sommer, Albert
Sommer, Ingeborg
Sommer, Kaspar
Sonneborn, M. Sonntagsblatt (Hamburg) Sontagsgesellschaft (Wattwil)
Sorokin, ?
Spachtholz, Otto Josef
Spakovsky, A. von
Spangenberg, Berthold
Specovius, Günther
Spengel, Rita
Spies, Emily
Spies, Gerty
Spies, Rudolf
Spletz, Oskar
Spolen, Gretel
Sporer, Georg
Sprengel, Rita
Springe, Freimut
Staatliche Werkakademie Kassel
Staatliches Landschulheim Marquartstein
Staatsministerium Buro fur Humatsdient
Stadelmayer
Stadler, Priska
Stadler, Wolf
Stadtbucherei München-Schwabing
Städtische Bühnen Bielefiedel
Städtische Bühnen München
Städtische Volkhochschule Oberhausen
Städtisches Gymnasium in Heine
Städtisches Kulturamt
Stadtmüller, G.
Stadttheater Ingolstadt
Stäglich, Dieter
Stählin, Rudolf
Stakhovich, Mariia Aleksandrovna
Stamm, Kurt
Stammler, Wolfgang
Standortälteste der Bundeswehr
Standortkommandantur (Ingolstadt, Mittenwald, Traunstein)
Stanfield, B. M.
Starytskii, V.
Stauber, Martin
Stauder, Gertrud
Stauder, Heinz
Stauffenberg, Graf Schenk von
Stebut, Peter von
Stedry, Vladimir
Steen, Hedwig
Stefanovich, Konstantin
Steidle, Robert
Steigner, J.
Stein, H. E.
Steinbach, Erich
Steinbauer, Wolfgang
Steinbüchel, Theodor
Steiner, Julia
Steingrüben Verlag
Steininger, Alexander
Steinwand, D. Eduard
Stellwag, ?
Stellzig, Helene
Stendorovskaia
Steppuhn, Albrecht
Steppuhn, Hans
Steppuhn, Luise
Stickelburger, Rudolf
Stiebler, Gerbert
Stifterbibliothek
Stiftung Europa
Stiftung Landerziehungsheim Neubeuern
Stillfried, Gebhard
Sting, Kurt
Stober, G. (Kreis der Freunde Paul Tillichs)
Stocker, Dieter
Stoian, P.
Stoltenberg, Hans L.
Stölzl, Anneliese
Stomberg, Ariane
Stone, Geoffrey
Stopinger, Siegfried
Storch Verlag
Storlinger, Otto
Stöver, Gerd
Straase, Bernd
Stradwitz, Maja
Straub, Therese and Gertrude
Strauss, Helène
Streitwieser, Elfriede
Strelka, Joseph
Streller, Justus
Strobel, Hans Rolf
Strocka, Michael
Ströhm, ?
Strommonger, Elly
Studenten-Filmstudio der Universität München
Studentenschaft Basel
Studentenschaft der technischen Hochschule München
Studentenvertretung der Medizinischen Akademie Düsseldorf
Studentische Filmfreunde an der Universität München
Studentischer Filmclub München
Studentsischer Filmkreis (Darmstadt)
Studentisches Kuratorium für Wiedervereinigung
Studio für Filmkunst
Studium Generale (Springer-Verlag)
Stülpnagel, Siegfried
Stümmer, Erich Stuttgarter Zeitung (Biedrzynski, Schoningh)
Süddeutsches Landestheater der Jugend
Süddeutsches Theater der Jugend
Südtiroler Kulturinstitut (Bozen)
Südwestfunk
Sulger, Leopold Summa Kulturphilosophische Gesprache Summa Verlag
Svetov, A.
Swiridoff, Paul
Swoboda, Marianne
Szankowska, A.
Tagespost Tarr, R. Die Tat Tchimorin, C.
Technische Hochschule Karlsruhe
Technische Hochschule. Studium general. Arbeitskreis Film)
Technische Universität Dresden (A. Weichold)
Terentiev, T.
Terres-Trip, Luise
Teucher, Eugen
Theatergemeinde Bonn
Theatergemeinde Köln
Theater Kassiererin (?)
Theatersammlung der Hansestadt Hamburg (Else Legband)
Theaterwissenschaftliche Sammlung der Universität (Erlangen)
Theens, Karl Thieme
Theologische Fachschaft Basel (Paul Helfenberger)
Thermal-Sol-Radiumbad Bad Münster
Theuermann, Karin
Thiel, Reinhold
Thiele, A.
Thielmann, Klaus von
Thieme, Ernst
Thieme, Sybille
Thieringer, Rolf
Thies, Hans Arthur
Thilenius, Dietmut
Thimm, Gerhard
Thom, Johannes
Thomas, Elsie
Thomé, Josef
Thomson, Erik
Tiemann, Bernhard
Tietze, Heinrich
Time-Life International (Enno Hobbing)
Timken-Zimkann, Stefanie K. and Reinhard P.
Timreck, Lusanne
Tirpitz, W. von
Titicheani (?), P.
Tobisch, Oswald O.
Tolstaia, Lidiia
Traub, Hedwig
Traub, Hermann
Traumenn, ?
Traut, Ludwig
Trem, Hilde
Trifels Verlag
Tronier Funder, C.
Trushnovich, A.
Tsaradkin, S.
Tsakonas, Dem.
TSchekunow, Georg (Chekunov)
TSchwertka, G. (IUrii Chvertka)
Tuiskonia
Ude, Karl (Welt und Wort)
Uhde, Ernst
Uhde-Bernays, Hermann
Ukrainian Youth Organization
Ulner, Martin
Unabhängige Hochschulgruppe für Wehrkunde
Uncic, K.
UNESCO
Unger, Elena
Union. Deutsche Verlagsgesellschaft Stuttgart Die Union. Monatsschrift der Union der leitenden Angestellten Universidad Nacional de Cordoba
Universitá di Napoli
Universität Basel. Theologische Fachschaft (P. Helfenberger)
Universität Bonn. Slavistisches Seminar (M. Woltner)
Universität Mainz (F. J. Rintelen)
Universität Münster (Sozialforschungsstelle)
Universitätsbuchhandlung Max Hueber
Universitetet Oslo. Det Praktisk-Theologiske Seminar
University of Illinois. Department of Russian (R. E. Matlaw)
Unterberger, E.
Unterberger, J.
Unverricht, Gabriel
Urania Berlin. Deutsche Kultur-Gemeinschaft (Otto Henning)
Uspenskii, N.
Uthe-Spencker, Joachim
Uvarova, N.
Vagtsenko, Vsevolod Petrovich
Val'denmaier, S.
Valentine, Mitchell and Company Limited
Val'ter, V.
Valters, Nikolaus
Vandenhoeck & Ruprecht Verlagsbuchhandlung (Göttingen)
Van der Meulen, Jan
Van Dyck, Gerty
Van Gelre, Henk
Velhagen und Klasings Monatshelfte
Verband der Angehörigen der Baltischen Ritterschaften (Peter Baron Korff)
Verband der Lehrer an der berufsbildenden Schulen der Pfalz
Verband der nordrheinischen Textilindustrie
Verband der Volkshochschulen des Landes Rheinland-Pfalz
Verband deutscher Studentenschaften
Verband oberer Angestellar der Gisen und Stahlindustrie
Verband oberer Bergbeamten
Verden-Göring, Georg
Verein Deutscher Ingenieure
Verein für Kunst und Wissenschaft
Verein für wissenschaftliche Vorlesungen
Verein Studenhilfe München
Verein "Ungarns Freiheit-Weltfrieden" (Konrad Richter)
Vereinigung des Katholischen Buchhandels
Vereno, Gertrude Maria (w/ Dr. Matthias)
Verkehrsverein Oberhausen
Verlag Albert Nauck & Co.
Verlag Bamberger Reiter
Verlag der Frankfurter Hefte
Verlag der Parma-Edition
Verlag deutscher Volksbücher
Verlag Dr. Schnell & Dr. Steiner
Verlag für Reicht und Gesellschaft (Basel)
Verlag für Wirtschaft und Sozialpolitik
Verlag Georg D. W. Callaway
Verlag Heim und Werk
Verlag Heinrich Ellermann
Verlag Hermann Rinn
Verlag Johann Wilhelm Naumann
Verlag J. Pfeiffer
Verlag Karl Alber Freiburg
Verlag Kultur und Fortschritt
Verlag Kurt Wesemeyer
Verlag Otto Walter
Verlag "Soziale Welt" (Dortmund)
Verlag Walter Lehning
Verlag Willi Weismann
Verlag W.Kohlhammer
Verlag Wolfgang Weidlich
Verlagsanstalt Benziger &g Co. (Zürich)
Verlagsbuchhandlung Ferdinand Schöningh
Verleger Union
Verwaltungs Lehrgang
Verwaltungs- und Wirschaftsakademie Industriebezurk
Veste Verlag
Vetter, Marga (nee Maischner)
Vierneisel, Emil
Vikt. Körper. Pelz-Modell-Haus
Villard, J. J.
Villinger, Carl J. H.
Vilsolz, Lili
Vishnevskii, V.
Voigtlander, Barliese
Vol'ia
Volkov, Igor Vasil'evich
Volksbildungskurse Glarus
Volksbildungsvereinung Forchheim
Volksbildungswerk (Erding)
Volksbildungswerk Kaufbeuren
Volksbildungswerk Nürtingen
Volksbildungswerk Villingen
Volksbühne Hannover
Volkshochschule Aalen
Volkshochschule Aschaffenburg
Volkshochschule Böblingen-Sindelfingen
Volkshochschule Braunschweig
Volkshochschule Ettlingen
Volkshochschule Gummersbach
Volkshochschule Herford
Volkshochschule Holzkirchen
Volkshochschule Kaufbeuren
Volkshochschule Landshut
Volkshochschule Münster
Volkshochschule Pullach
Volkshochschule Schwenningen
Volkshochschule Singen
Volkshochschule Traunstein
Volkshochschule und Jugendbildungswerk der Stadt Ingelheim/Rhein.
Volkshochschule Wolfenbüttel
Volksritter
Vollmer, M.
Vorbereitender Ausschus des Exil-Penzentrums in der Bundesrepublik
Vorbildungskurse für Journalisten
Vordtriede, Käthe
Voronovskii, Dimitrii von
Vorsteheramt der Brüdergemeine
Vortragsvermittlung
Vortriede, Werner
Voss, Adolf
Vossschulte, K.
Vucic, Käthe
Vyrubel (?), A.
Wachsmuth, R.
Wachtmann, Hans Günter
Wagner, Fritz (Ende. Redaktion und Anfang)
Wagner, Helmut
Wagner, Wilhelm
Waldmann, Guido
Walker, James and Jytte
Wallenheiter, Christian
Walltor-Verlag (Gideon Schüler)
Walter, R. von
Walter, ?
Walter de Gruyter
Walter G. Mühlau
Walther, Frieda
Walther, Paul
Walz, R.
Wartezimmer
Weber, Adolf
Weddigen, W.
Wedenjapin, N. (N. Vedeniapin)
Wegner, Willy
Wehrebereichskommando
Wehrt, Brigitte
Wehrt, Hartmut
Weidemann, Kurt
Weidemann, Olga
Weidhaas, Th.
Weidlich, Wolfgang
Weigert, J.
Weinheimer Senioren Convent
Weinreis, Käthe
Weisbender, Anneliese
Weismantel, Leo
Weiss, Andreas von
Weitzenberg, A. O.
Welch, H. A.
Weldler, Norbert Welt am Sonntag Die Welt der Slaven Welt im Gespräch Welt und Wort Welt am Sonntag Weltläufer. Cursor Mundi (R. Lauth)
Wendelstadt, Herta
Wendt, ?
Wenzl, A.
Werber, Karl Gunter
Werdohl, Stadtverwaltung
Werkgemeinschaften christlicher Arbeitnehmer
Wersebe, ? von
Wesely, Josef
Wesendank, Alador von Westdeutsche Allgemeine Westdeutscher Rundfunk
Westdeutscher Verlag
Westfälischer Industrie-Klub zu Dortmund
Westhoff-Niemeyer, Hilde
Wetter (City)
Wheelis, Sigrid M.
Wichmann, ?
Wiedemann, Albert
Wiedemann, Käthe
Wiedemann, Olga
Wiedmann, ?
Wieja, Klaus
Wieszner, Georg Gustav
Wilberg, Hans Joachim
Wilczynski, Jan
Wild, Gerhard
Wildman, Allan and Helga
Wilhelm, Rudolf M. E.
Will, Günter
Wille, Klaus and Claudia
Willecke, Eberhard
Williams, Robert
Winckel, P. aus dem
Winkel, H. J. zum
Winkler, E.
Winkler Verlag
Wippern, Hans
Wirsing, Annelis
Wirsing, Giselher
Wirtschaftsgilde
Wirtschaftsverband Münchner Buchhändler Wissenschaft und Weltbild Wissenschaftliche Auskunftei
Wissenschaftliche Buchgesellschaft
Wissenschaftliche Buchgemeinschaft
Wissenschaftliche Verlagsgesellschaft
Wissenschaftliche Vortragsgemeinschaft
Wissenschaftlicher Forschungs- und Lehrstab
Wissenschaftlicher Verein
Wittig, H.E.
Wittslock, Nora-Liane
Woebs, M.
Woefurt, Kurt von
Wolff, E.
Wolff, Marga
Wolter, Gerhard
Wolters, Jürgen-Detlef
Wortelmann, Fritz
Wühr, Wilhelm
Wulf, Heinz
Wunderle, Georg
Wünzel, F.X.
Würfel, Kurt
Wurstner, Theo
Württembergische Akademie für Erziehung und Unterricht
Württembergische Landesbibliothek
Württembergische Staatstheater Stüttgart
Wüst
Zacharias, Paul
Zakharii, Otets
Zänker, ??
Zastrow, Roswitha
Zeffler, Helmut
Zehnte interantionale Theaterwoch
Zeibig, Max
Zeiner-Henrikson, R. Zeitschrift fur philosophischer Forschung Zenker, C.
Zenker, Ed.
Zentralfachschule der duetschen Susswarenwirtschaft
Zentralstelle des Borromäusvereins
Ziegler, Martha
Zigel', I.
Zillman, Horst
Zimmerman, Paul F.
Zinke, Herbert
Zinn, K.
Zion Lutheran Church
Zitzewitz, S.
Zocher, Rudolf
Zorn, Rudolf
Zuckmayer, Gisela
Zuckermayer, Thea
Authors, Exiled; Authors, Russian -- 20th Century -- Archives; Authors, Russian -- 20th Century; Political refugees -- Soviet Union; Russian literature -- 20th Century; Russia -- Emigration and immigration; Photographs; Sketches; Ioann, Archbishop of San Francisco and Western United States, 1902-1989; Adamovich, Georgiĭ, 1892-1972; Aldanov, Mark Aleksandrovich, 1886-1957; Arsenʹev, Nikolaĭ Sergeevich, 1888-1977; Benz, Ernst, 1907-1978; Berberova, N. (Nina), 1901-1993; Berdi͡aev, Nikolaĭ, 1874-1948; Bunin, Ivan Alekseevich, 1870-1953; Florovsky, Georges, 1893-1979; Frank, Tatʹi︠a︡na; Frank, Viktor, 1909-1972; Gadamer, Frida; Gadamer, Hans-Georg, 1900-2002; Gulʹ, Roman, 1896-1986; Heiseler, Bernt von, 1907-; Heiseler, Gertrude; Horkheimer, Max, 1895-1973; Ivanov, Lidiia; Ivanov, Sergeĭ; Ivanov, V. I. (Vi͡acheslav Ivanovich), 1866-1949; Ivask, I︠U︡riĭ, 1907-1986; Karpovich, Michael, 1888-1959; Kerensky, Aleksandr Fyodorovich, 1881-1970; Klum, Edith; Kroner, Alice; Kroner, Richard, 1884-1974; Kühn, Johannes, 1934-; Leontovitsch, Victor, 1902-1959; Lilienfeld, Fairy von, 1917-2009; Losskiĭ, N. O. (Nikolaĭ Onufrievich), 1870-1965; Lowrie, Donald A. (Donald Alexander), 1889-1974; Luther, Arthur, 1876-1955; Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955; Maurin̦a, Zenta, 1897-1978; McFalls, Richard; Medtner, Anna Mikhaĭlovna, 1877-1965; Melʹgunov, S. P. (Sergeĭ Petrovich), 1879-1956; Mildner, Irmengard; Mildner, Paul, 1955-; Morozov, Ivan, 1883-1942; Müller, Ludolf, 1917-2009; Muromt͡seva-Bunina, V. N. (Vera Nikolaevna), 1881-1961; Neumann, Carl, 1832-1925; Nikolśkaia, Natalía Nikolaevna; Paeschke, Hans; Pasternak, Boris Leonidovich, 1890-1960; Piroschkow, Vera, 1921-; Poltorat︠s︡kiĭ, N. P. (Nikolaĭ Petrovich), 1921-1990; Rzhevskiĭ, Leonid, 1905-1986; Saemisch, Ernesto, 1902-1984; Shcherbatov, Sergeĭ, kni︠a︡zʹ, 1875-1962; Stammler, Heinrich A.; Steininger, Alexander, 1930-; Stepun, Fedor, 1884-1965; Struve, Gleb, 1898-1985; Taube, Otto, Freiherr von, 1879-; Tillich, Hannah; Tillich, Paul, 1886-1965; Tschižewskij, Dmitrij, 1894-1977; Ulʹi͡anov, N. (Nikolaĭ), 1904-1985; Varshavskiĭ, V. S. (Vladimir Sergeevich), 1906-; Veĭdle, V., 1895-1979; Vishni︠a︡k, M. V. (Mark Venʹi︠a︡minovich), 1883-1977; Vodov, S.; Zaĭt︠s︡ev, Boris, 1881-1972; Zander, L. A. (Leon Alexander), 1893-1964; Zenʹkovskiĭ, V. V. (Vasiliĭ Vasilʹevich), 1881-1962; Zernov, Nicolas, 1898-1980; Zurov, Leonid, 1902-1971; Institut für Filmwesen; Tolstoy Foundation (Germany)
- Correspondence, 1943-65; Series I; 16; (41 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent, and then chronologically. For an index to correspondent names filed in the "A-Z" General files, see the Appendix.
  - GENERAL FILES
    - "A" General, 1945-64, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - _ Abendländische Akademie, 1953-63 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Abendroth, Walter, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Adamovich, Georgii, 1964 Feb 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Adelheim, Serge, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Scope and Contents
        Also spelled: Sergei Viktorovich Adel'geim. Includes typescript on B. Pasternak
    - _ Adler, Nina, 1953-64, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
      - Adolph, R., 1947-50 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Adolphi, Roland Herman Adelphi, Ursula (nee Rogge), 1960-62 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Aegis Verlag, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - AFCENT (Allied Forces in Central Europe), 1961-62 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Agafonov, Ivan, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Agentur des Rauhen Hauses (G. Wolter), 1952-53 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Akademische Auslandsstelle München (G. Pflüger), 1954-59 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - _ Albertus-Magnus-Vereinigung, 1952-56 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - _ Albrecht, Renate, 1949-64 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Aldanov, Mark Aleksandrovich, 1955-57 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        Pseudonym of M. Landau
      - Aleksandr, Arkhiepiskop Berlinskii i Germanskii, 1954-64 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Alimov, Nikolai, 1956-63 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - _ Allgemeiner Studenten-Ausschus der (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Ludwig Maximilian-Universität München, 1956-57, n.d.
      - American Friends of Russian Freedom, 1959-61 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        Includes: T. Prigorovskaia
      - American Friends Service Committee, 1949-52 (Box 1, Folder 23)
        Includes: Quäker Studenten Stuben
    - _ Amerika-Haus (Augsburg, Bremen (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Darmstadt), 1953-58
    - _ Amerika-Haus (Hamburg, Hannover (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Heidelberg, Hof/Saale), 1953-57
    - _ Amerika-Haus (München), 1953-58 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - _ Amerika-Haus (Nürnberg, Wiesbaden (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Würzburg), 1953-60
      - Amerikanische Lesehall, 1950-51 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Anckerle, G., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - _ Andreev, N., 1955-62 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Angelander, V., 1944 Jun 11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Annenkova, Varvara Pavlovna, 1953-64 (Box 1, Folder 32)
        Also known as: Barbara von Annenkoff
    - _ Apanasov, Petr, 1955-63, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Apel, Nina, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Appel, Hermann, 1963-64 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Arbeitsgeberverband für die Eisen- und Metallindustrie des Rheinisch- Westfälischen Industriebezirks, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Arbeitsgemeinschaft "Evangelium und Geistesleben", 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Katholischer Laienwerke, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Arbeitsgemeinschaft sozialdemokratischer Akademiker, 1958-61 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Archiv für Rechts- und Sozialphilosophie, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Argiva Verlag, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Arnan, Elizabeth, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Arsen'ev, IUrii Sergeevich, 1960-64 (Box 2, Folder 43)
        Includes holograph "Obnovlenie interesa k drevnei russkoi ikonopisi"
    - _ Arsen'ev, Nikolai Sergeevich (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
      - Arsen'eva, O. Arsenv'ev, IUrii, 1944-64, n.d.
        Includes typescript
    - _ Assmann, Eugen, 1949-60 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Association Nicolas Berdiaeff, 1952-54 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Auer, Alfons, 1946-47 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Augsburg, Germany, 1950-55 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Augustin, Annamarie, 1956-61, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Augustinuswerk (Hamburg), 1949 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Aussen-Institut, 1951-52 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Autenrieth, Johanna, 1949-64 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Averino, Z., 1951-52, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - "B" General, 1946-64, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 55-61)
      - Baden-Baden. Kurdirektion, 1952-54 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Balmashev, M., 1953-55 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Bannaski, Heinz Bannaski, Barbara, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Bannert, Magda, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Barloewen, Hildegard von, 1963-64 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Barsov, Vasilii Pavlovich, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 67)
        Also spelled: Wass. Barssoff
      - Bartz, Rudolf, 1949-64 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Bauer, Johann Erwin, 1956-58 (Box 3, Folder 69)
        Includes typescripts
    - _ Bauer, Ruth (nee Malhotra), 1955-64, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 70-72)
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also: Ernst Saemisch
    - _ Bauer, Walter, 1946-64 (Box 3, Folder 73-75)
      - Baum, Hans, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - Bäumler, Ernst, 1962-64 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Bayerische Vereinsbank, 1959-61 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Bayerischer Jugendring, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Bayerischer Kunstgewerbe-Verein, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Bayerischer Landesverband für Freie Volksbildung, 1952-53 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Bayerischer Landwirtschaftsverlag, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Bayerischer Ministerpräsident, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - _ Bayerischer Rundfunk, 1947-65 (Box 3, Folder 84)
      Includes: H. Händler
    - _ Bayerisches Staatsministerium der (Box 3, Folder 85)
      - Justiz, 1954-57
    - _ Bayerisches Staatsministerium für (Box 3, Folder 86)
      - Unterricht und Kultus, 1946-64
      - Beck, Eugen, 1949-55 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Beckerath, Hermann von, 1951-64 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Beckerath, Aenne von
      - Beha, Fee, 1953-55, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - Behmisch, Franz Joachim, 1950-54 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - Behrens, H., 1953-61 (Box 4, Folder 91)
      - Beiersdorf, Woldemar, 1958-63 (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Bellot family, 1954-64 (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - Belotsvetov, A., 1946-53 (Box 4, Folder 94)
      - Belotsvetov, N.
      - Bem, A., 1944 Apr 16 (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - _ Benz, Ernst, 1951-64, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 96)
        Includes: Kommission für Kirchengeschichte, Ökumenisches Seminar der Theologischen Fakultät der Philipps-Universität Marburg- Lahn
      - Berberova, Nina Nikolaevna, 1958 Jan 18 (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - Berg, Emmy von, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Bergerot, Henry, 1961-63 (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - _ Berkenkopf, Galina (Box 4, Folder 100)
        - Berkenkopf, Paul, 1949-64
      - Bernsdorf, Wilhelm, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 101)
      - Bernt, Walther, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 102)
      - Berthold, Eugen, 1947-52 (Box 4, Folder 103)
      - _ Bertrand, Karen, 1944-53 (Box 4, Folder 104-105)
        - Die Besinnung, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 106)
      - Beste, Elisabeth, 1950-53 (Box 4, Folder 107)
      - _ Beste, Elsbeth, 1950-64, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 108)
      - _ Beste, Theodor, 1946-65, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 109-111)
        - Beste, Ursula, 1950-64, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 112)
          Includes correspondence by Elisabeth Beste
      - _ Beste family, 1946-64 (Box 4, Folder 113)
      - _ Biener, Jessie, 1944-65, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 114-120)
      - _ Bienert, Ida, 1944-62, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 121)
        Also known as: Ida Fedorowna Bienart
      - Biennale di Venezia Mostra Internationale d'Arte Cinematografiea, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 122)
      - Bigi, A. M., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 123)
      - Bircele, Angelika, 1946-49 (Box 5, Folder 124)
      - Blagov, V., 1951-53 (Box 5, Folder 125)
      - Blarr, Oskar Gottlieb, 1955-56 (Box 5, Folder 126)
      - Boehm, Lydia, 1953 Aug 15 (Box 5, Folder 127)
        Includes clippings
      - Boev, Vsevolod Nikolaevich, 1946-51 (Box 5, Folder 128)
      - Bohlsen, Gerhard, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 129)
      - Böhme, Ellen, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 130)
      - Böhringer, A. E., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 131)
      - Bol'shukhin, IUrii IAkovlevich, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 132)
        Pseudonym of IU. IA. Kandiev
        See also: Svoboda
      - Böning, Horst, 1954-61 (Box 5, Folder 133)
      - Bonn (City), 1957-59 (Box 5, Folder 134)
      - Bormann, Lutz, 1954-55 (Box 5, Folder 135)
      - Brant, Marusia, 1953, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 136)
      - Braun, Peter, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 137)
      - Breithaupt, Inge, 1951-63 (Box 5, Folder 138)
      - Breithaupt, Hans
      - Bremen, S. von, 1962-64 (Box 5, Folder 139)
      - _ Bremer Volkshochschule, 1952-56 (Box 5, Folder 140)
        - Breitschneider, Lotte, 1955-56 (Box 5, Folder 141)